Kontakt

martin.mateju23@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/martinmateju-2164a58b (LinkedIn)

Nejčastější dovednosti

JetBrains MPS

Python

JavaScript

Languages

English (Full Professional)

Czech (Native or Bilingual)

German (Limited Working)

Danish (Professional Working)

Certifications

Testing with Agile

Big Data Modeling and Management Systems

Managing an Agile Team

MTA: Software Development Fundamentals

Martin Mateju

Software Engineer

Česko

Souhrn

Originally, I started as a business student, however my personal interests brought me to study Computer Science. Over the years of my education I've gained skills and experience within the area of software design, large scale systems, big data and machine learning. I enjoy working as a developer, especially when I get a chance to work on complex tasks or learn something new.

Pracovní zkušenosti

Amaris Consulting Software Developer března 2022 - října 2024 (2 roky 8 měsíců)

Prague, Czechia

Working as a software developer in automotive industry. Currently I'm working with meta programing system e.g. Jetbrains MPS.

MountainLift Software Developer října 2022 - prosince 2022 (3 měsíce) Prague, Czechia

Oracle

Software Developer února 2020 - ledna 2022 (2 roky)

I joined Tooling and Automation team, where I work as a full-stack developer using Python and ReactJS.

SMART-TRIAL

Junior Software Developer října 2018 - ledna 2020 (1 rok 4 měsíce) Aalborg, Northern Region, Denmark

I joined MEDEI ApS as a full-stack developer to support development of SMART-TRIAL project. I worked primarily with MEAN stack (AngularJs, Express, NodeJS/Typescript, MongoDB).

Intel Corporation Student Software Developer C++ června 2017 - září 2018 (1 rok 4 měsíce) Aalborg

I was a member of the antenna tuning team at Intel Mobile Telecomunications in Aalborg, where I worked as a tooling developer for the antennas and as a administrator of prior antenna tools generations. I worked primarily with C++(Qt framework), Python, Matlab.

InterContinental Hotels & Resorts Sales and Marketing - Intern srpna 2014 - října 2014 (3 měsíce) Hlavní město Praha, Česká republika

During my internship period I was a part of the Sales & Marketing Department at InterContinental Prague Hotel for 3 months. During my internship, I worked mainly with hotel booking and sales programs. Futhermore, I assisted with the preparation for the hotel's 40th anniversary, where I researched for the suppliers and negotiated prices with them. In addition to that, I assisted with the marketing plan for the anniversary of the hotel.

Vzdělání

UCN, Professionshøjskolen University College Nordjylland Bachelor's degree - Software Development · (2018 - 2019)

UCN, Professionshøjskolen University College Nordjylland Academy Profession Degree, Computer Science · (2015 - 2018)

UCN, Professionshøjskolen University College Nordjylland Academic profesional degree, Tourism and Travel Service Management · (2013 - 2015)

Business Academy Eldo

High school education, Business, Management, Marketing, and Related Support Services · (2009 - 2013)